**Field Researcher Alpha** Privacy Policy
=========================================

**Last updated:** 09/05/2023

**Effective date:** 10/05/2023

Thank you for using **Field Researcher Alpha**! We are committed to protecting your privacy and complying with all applicable laws and regulations.

**Field Researcher Alpha** is the official **Tickets-Plus** repository's public instance.

#### Information We Collect:

* Guild settings provided by the administrators, including guild\_id and configuration information.
* Ticket information, including channel\_id, guild\_id, user\_id (of the creator if provided by Integration), date\_created, last\_response, and ticket-specific settings and internal values.
* Tags – short, formatted snippets of text, associated with a 'key', and with optional embed parameters.
* Member information, including guild\_id, user\_id and what status the member has in the guild and for how long.
* User information, including user\_id and whether the user is an owner.

#### How We Use Your Information:

* We use the information we collect to facilitate the bot's functionality and provide support to our users.
* We do not store any personally identifiable information, as per Discord's classification of User IDs not being PIIs.

#### Cache:

The bot automatically caches information from the Discord API gateway to facilitate functionality. The cache is automatically cleared when the bot is restarted and is not stored long-term.

#### Third-Party Links:

Our privacy policy does not apply to third-party links or services provided by other companies or individuals. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of any third-party links or services you use or access

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy:

We reserve the right to modify or update our privacy policy at any time. Changes will be posted on the official **Tickets-Plus** repository and the updated date will be indicated at the top of the policy

##### Contact Us:

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us at tos.tickets-plus at techttgames.dev

Additionally, should you wish to export your data or delete any information, please contact us using the above email.

© 2023-present _Tickets+ Contributors_. All rights reserved.
